indiegamemag.com 2014-12-09

# Privacy Policy | Indie Game Magazine

**Purchases –** We don’t see or store financial stuff.

All your purchase transactions are handled by secure payment providers and reliable partners (namely Magcloud, Fastspring, and Paypal). Magcloud is owned by HP – [they have a ton of fancy badges and seals](http://welcome.hp.com/country/us/en/privacy.html) and handle the printing and processing of our magazines. [Paypal ](https://cms.paypal.com/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Privacy_full&locale.x=en_US)and [Fastspring ](http://www.fastspring.com/privacy.php)are both well respected payment providers. Indie Game Mag  **DOES NOT** store  **ANY** credit card numbers, names, or financial information, in fact we  **NEVER EVEN SEE** any of your credit information. For more information on our Payment Service Partner’s please see their privacy policies above.

**Our Site and Newsletter** – We do collect email addresses, usernames, and customer info but we won’t sell it!

Visitors may provide us with email addresses, usernames, names, addresses, and other information to us when they sign up with our site, newsletter, or forums.  IGM has the right to save this information so that they can track and correspond with its readers and customers.  We promise to never share, sell or rent this information.  All personal identifiable information is used strictly for customer service and interaction.

Our site allows users to display some information publicly (author bios, web links, etc) on our site. Users are responsible for information that they decide to share publicly and will not hold IGM liable.

**Web Statistics** – We collect anonymous info about stuff and use it like any other site.

Web statistics are collected and calculated by our hosting service and google. Information such as IP address, unique users, web browser, operating system, pages accessed on our site, duration of stay, etc. are logged and collected. This information is solely used for general internet traffic tracking and so that we may assess and improve our website. It is anonymous and none of your personal information is ever used or in danger.

**Links-** teh internets is a big scary place and we only control this little oasis.

This privacy statement only applies to this website. There are links to other sites that IGM does not control. We are not responsible for the privacy statements of other sites. This privacy statement only applies to the information collected on this site. For information on linked sites’ privacy statements please refer to their websites. Thank you.

**Ads-  **You gotta spend money to make money.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**COPPA-  **Get to da COPPA!  

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.  

* * *
